{
  "level": 5,
  "unit": 6,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "A ____________ is a short announcement of the latest news.",
          "answer": "bulletin"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ are gifts of money, time, or effort given to a cause.",
          "answer": "contributions"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ is a great difference or variety.",
          "answer": "diversity"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When people ____________, they joined the armed forces of their own free will.",
          "answer": "enlisted"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you ____________ something, you stop it from moving from one place to another.",
          "answer": "intercept"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ are plans or processes for doing something.",
          "answer": "operations"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ are new members of the armed forces.",
          "answer": "recruits"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ is finding a way to live.",
          "answer": "survival"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "An ____________ is a change in a plant or animal that helps it survive.",
          "answer": "adaptation"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you are ____________, you are able to move and react quickly and easily.",
          "answer": "agile"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you ____________ something, you hide or store it in a hiding place.",
          "answer": "cache"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When something is ____________, it is temporarily inactive.",
          "answer": "dormant"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When animals ____________, they hunt or search for food.",
          "answer": "forage"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If the temperature is ____________, it is very cold.",
          "answer": "frigid"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When animals ____________, they spend the winter sleeping.",
          "answer": "hibernate"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An animal’s fur ____________, or keeps the animal warm.",
          "answer": "insulates"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "If something ____________, it makes a loud, harsh sound.",
          "answer": "blares"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ____________ is a relationship or bond with someone or something.",
          "answer": "connection"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An ____________ is a short trip to do or get something.",
          "answer": "errand"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An ____________ is the giving of one thing for another.",
          "answer": "exchange"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ is repeating words with the same vowel sound.",
          "answer": "assonance"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A poem with ____________ has words that contain the same middle or final",
          "answer": "consonance"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When writers use ____________, they use words to create a picture.",
          "answer": "imagery"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "____________ is giving human qualities to things that aren’t human, such as objects or animals.",
          "answer": "personification"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
